

CONTACT ME AT

- Hietaniemenkatu 8 A9 00100 HELSINKI
- dasilva.alan@outlook.com
- alandsilva.github.io
- in linkedin.com/in/alandsilva

SKILLS SUMMARY

- ●●●● Full Stack web development
- •••• Databases
- ••• Docker

LANGUAGE SKILLS

- English native
- Portuguese native
- Finnish good

ALAN DA SILVA

IT STUDENT

PERSONAL PROFILE

I'm an IT student at Oulu University of Applied Sciences, where I have gained experience in developing applications, from planning to final product. Technologies I have experience with are React, Node.js, MongoDB, MySQL, Firebase, Docker.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Early-morning newspaper deliverer

Posti Group Oy | May 2021 - November 2021

• Distributing newspapers in Helsinki area

Early-morning newspaper deliverer

Posti Group Oy | August 2020 - January 2021

• Distributing newspapers in Helsinki area

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Oulu University of Applied Sciences

Information Technology | August 2019 -

- Studies include web development, mobile development and IoT.
- Projects developing applications and services.

Full Stack open 2021

Certificates:

- Full Stack : <u>certificate</u>
- Containers Docker and Docker Compose: <u>certificate</u>
- GraphQL: certificate

HOBBIES

The Institute of Adult Education in Helsinki

Finnish language course | September 2021 - December 2021

Studying Finnish from level A2 to level B1